Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1935-2002.
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-2002.
- Series IV. Cornell administration activities
  - Development and corporate relations
    - Noyes, N.H. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Ohrbach, J.K. (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Olin, J.M. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Olin, S.T. (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Owings, N.A. - 1 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Owings, N.A. - 2 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Pew Family (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Price, Olive B. (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Purcell, Robert William (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, Robert W. Purcell, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Rockwell, George and Mary P. (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Scheetz, Mrs. Henry F. (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Snee, Mrs. Katherine (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Suter, Albert E. (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Sinclaire, R.O. (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Upson, Mr. and Mrs. Maxwell Mayhew (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Uris, H. (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Van Cleve, Mr. and Mrs. Herman (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Vollmer, Gus (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Vinik's Visit, June 3, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Weinhold, Julius (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - West, John D. (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Wetzel, Harry (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - White, E.B. (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Withrow, James R. Jr. (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Foundations, Misc. (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - AMOCO (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Exxon Education Foundation (Box 24, Folder 59-61)
    - Fairchild Foundation (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Guggenheim (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Kresge Foundation (Box 24, Folder 65-66)
    - Mellon Foundation (Box 24, Folder 67-68)
    - Merrill Trust Foundation (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Phillips Foundation (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Teagle Foundation (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Tinker Foundation (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Library Advisory Council (LAC)
    - Hill, Kenneth - Background Information (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - John Lyon Collyer Brochure (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - LAC - Drafts (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Expenditures and Resources of ARL University Libraries, FY, 1976-1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Description (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Drafts of Organization Letters for Library Council (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Library Associates Invitation Brochure (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Memo from Colman to Kennedy re President's Records, Apr. 30, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Members of LAC (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - LAC Meeting, May 1982 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Invitation Responses (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Reflections of Joel Sibley after Meeting, May 14, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - E.H. Blecckwell, Seal and Serpent Society (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - LAC (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Fall LAC Meeting, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Gould Colman (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Cornell University Libraries (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Update on Automation - RLG/RLIN (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - LAC Meeting, Apr. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Spring Meeting Memo, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - B.B. Adam's Thoughts after Meeting, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Memo, May 16, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Rhodes at Fall Meeting, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Report of LAC (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - LAC, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Robison Library Committee (Box 25, Folder 27-28)
  - Music Committee
    - Music Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Music, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 30-31)
    - Music, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Music, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Music, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Music, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Music, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Music, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 37-38)
    - Music, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Music, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Fund for Quality Concerts (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Music, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Music Committee, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Music Misc., 1984 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Ticket Prices, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Financial Estimate, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Music Misc., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Ticket Prices, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Ticket Sale Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Final Ticket Prices, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Music Committee - Letter from A. Groos to W. Herbster, Mar. 9, Mar. 22, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Fund for Quality Concerts, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Pres. Rhodes' Gift, Jan. 1982 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Memo: Estimated Income and Expense for 1981-1982, Oct. 30, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Reports by the Faculty Committee on Music, Sept. 1981 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Statler and Bailey Series, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Memo: 1981-1982 Ticket Prices, Dec. 18, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Working Papers on Ticket Sales, Prices, Financial Reports, etc., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Music Committee - Rehabilitation of Bailey Hall, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Concert Manager (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Music Committee - Minutes of Meetings (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Music Committee, Misc. (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Music Committee Memos - Present Estimate of 1980-1981 Deficit, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - DRC's Memo re Ticket Prices, Sept. 29, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Music Committee - DRC's Memos re 1980-1981 Deficit, 180-1981 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Cornell history
    - Cornell History (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Seventy Years of Physics at Cornell, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - If Murphy Were A Cornellian (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Arecibo
    - Cornell-Sydney University Astronomy Center, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Arecibo Advisory Board, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Arecibo Advisory Board, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - AAB Meeting, Cerromar Beach Hotel, Dec. 9-10, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Users Manual for the Arecibo Observatory, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - AAB Meeting, Cerromar Beach Hotel, Nov. 3-4, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 13th AAB Meeting, Ithaca NY, May 31-June 1, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Arecibo, 1984-1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - NAIC Arecibo Advisory Board, 1978-1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - NAIC Arecibo Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - NAIC Arecibo Advisory Board, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Lalonde Memorial, Nov. 25, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Arecibo, Dec. 11-12, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Arecibo Project, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Arecibo Meeting Papers, Dec. 9-10, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Inauguration of Arecibo Gregorian Telescope, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Deep Springs/Telluride
    - Students (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Co-Education Commission (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Misc. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Financial Report, 1977-1978; 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Minutes of the 1978 and 1979 Convention, Telluride Association, 1978, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Report of the Trustee Committee on Co-Education, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Minutes of the 1979 and 1980 Convention, Telluride Association, 1979, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Sunrose Design Group Design Proposal (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Statement on Co-Education and Sections I and II of Wesleyan University's Study of Educational Policies and Programs (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Motivation: Key to Educational Problems by R.B. Aird (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Sunrose Design Group Design Proposal (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Self-Study Report (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Report - Among the Few (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Accreditation Report (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Use of Alcohol (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Will Masters (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - "Education and Solipsism" by David Schuman (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Sundial (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Sundial, continued (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Robert J. Pulliam (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Co-Ed Issue, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Christopher Neri Breiseth (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Newsletter (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Trustees (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Deep Springs, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Deep Springs, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - DR. Robert B. Aird (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Constitution of Deep Springs and the Deed of Trust; also other Brochures (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Misc. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Reich (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Student activism and other Vietnam-era issues
    - Willard Straight Hall Takeover - Meeting in the Mayor's Office, DRC Notes, Mar. 24, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - "Why Did Perkins Fail?" (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Material on Straight Takeover, 1990's (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re Donald Downs Book, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - DRC on His Role as Provost in 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - 10th Anniversary - R.D. Miller, Willard Straight, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Ithaca Journal Articles, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Sun Articles: African-American Studies Program and the African-American Society (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Sun Articles: Residential Club Fire, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Articles: Anti-War Sentiments, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Sun Articles: Athletic Cutbacks, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous administration notes
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1960's (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Misc. Admin. Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Emergency Phone Tree, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Series V. National and international activities and interests
  - Higher education files
    - Higher Education, 1977-1982, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Cost of Higher Education, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - A.C.E. - NY State Panel (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Assoc. for Academic Health Centers, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Assoc. of American Universities, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - University of California Engr. Committee, 1968-1981 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - University of California Engr. Committee, 1968-1981 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - CHEAR Conference (IIE), Brazil, Feb. 27, 1972-Mar. 3, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - CHEAR Conference, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - CHEAR Conference, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - University of Cincinnati, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Clarkson College of Tech., 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Clarkson College of Tech., 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - University of Colorado, 1961-1989 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Columbia University, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Assoc. of Commonwealth Univ. Mtgs. - Edenburgh/Exeter, Aug. 1973 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Assoc. of Commonwealth Univ. Mtgs. - Edenburgh/Exeter, Aug. 1973 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - European Council of International Schools, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Hamilton College Hon. Degree, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Historically Black Colleges and Universities, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Hobart and William Smith Colleges, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Howard University, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - University of Illinois, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - International Association of Universities Conference, Moscow, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Ivy League Presidents, Meeting on Athletics (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - University of Kansas, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Lafayette College, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Latin America, 1982; 1965-1967 (Box 27, Folder 59A)
    - MIT, 1983-1993 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Mohawk Valley Community College, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - National Security Agency Meeting, Washington D.C., May 17, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Newcomen Society in North America, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Ohio State Seminar, June 1976 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Ohio State University, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Oklahoma Symposium, Oct. 1966 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - University of Oregon, 1968-1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Penn State, 1965-1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Pikeville College, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - University of Pittsburgh, DRC Pers., 1966, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Consulting work - University of Puerto Rico (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - RPI Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Rensselaer, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Retirement (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Rutgers University, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Rutgers University, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Study Panel - Housatonic Comm. Call - University of Bridgeport (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - TC3 Study Community, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - TC3 Study Community, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Wang Institute, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Wilkes University, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - China
    - Sub-subseries: Administrative files and correspondence
      - Organization of the Ministry of Education of China (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Statistics of Chinese Education, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Key Universities and Colleges of the PRC, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - China, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Equipment, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Beginnings of Panel, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Memo of Understanding between MOE and NAS, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Terms of Reference (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - CSCPRC Semi Annual Meetings, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Model Chinese-American Institute for Condensed Matter and Physical Quantum Electronics, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Costs, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Regulations Concerning Academic Degrees in the PRC, Apr. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - PRC - Application for Visas, June 1982 (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - 1982 Detention of American Student in Beijing, June 1982 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - Draft Agreements, June-July 1982 (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - Agreement, Aug.-Sept. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Paribas International, Sept. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - Perry-Smith Memo re Contract, Sept. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      - Tokyo Agenda, Sept. 4-6, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - S.Z. Sung to A.H. Weegle - World Bank Memo re UDP, Sept. 30, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - Model Universities, Oct. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 37)
      - Doctoral Degree Programs, Nov. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 38)
      - Ministerial Management Component, Nov. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 39)
      - Zhang Jien Lecture for Joint Meeting, Nov. 21, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 40)
      - Plan Trip, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 41)
      - Essentials and Schedule for China Mission, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 42)
      - Trip Report, Nov. 1982-Dec. 1982 (Box 28, Folder 43)
      - Nanjing Meeting, Dec. 1-4, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 44)
      - Educational Progress in China, 1949-1983 (Box 28, Folder 45)
      - "Information and Development Unit of the MOE of the PRC", 1983 (Box 28, Folder 46)
      - Key Points of Working Plan, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 47)
      - Alvin Eurich, Jan. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 48)
      - NAS China and Science Policy, Jan. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 49)
      - Dewey Experiment - Educational Reform and Political power by Barry Keenan, Jan. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 50)
      - DRC Memo, Feb. 17, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 51)
      - Letter from Liu Daoyu, President, Wuhan University, Feb. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 52)
      - DRC Memo, Feb. 21, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 53)
      - Pan Am Refund, Mar. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 54)
      - DRC Memo to MOE re Trip, Mar.-Apr. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 55)
      - DRC Memo to IAP re Trip, Mar.-Apr. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 56)
      - Trip Report, Mar.-Apr. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 57)
      - UN Programs in Chinese Universities, Apr. 19, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 58)
      - Farner Memo, Apr. 22, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 59)
      - Beemer Memo to President White, Apr. 27, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 60)
      - Project Universities, May 1983 (Box 28, Folder 61)
      - TecQuip International Limited, May 1983 (Box 28, Folder 62)
      - Beemer Memo to IAP re Corson Observations on Recent Trip, May 13, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 63)
      - Beemer Memo to IAP re Statler Observations on Recent Trip, May 13, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 64)
      - Mar.-Apr. 1983 in China; June 1983 Meeting in Paris, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 65)
      - China Joint Meeting, Paris, June 8-10, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 66)
      - Paris Trip, June 1983 (Box 28, Folder 67)
      - Amendment to Agreement, July 1983 (Box 28, Folder 68)
      - Beemer Memo - Meeting of International China Information Committee, Aug. 9, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 69)
      - Fall Itinerary, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 70)
      - Photos, Oct. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 71)
      - Correspondence, M.D. Morris, Nov. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 72)
      - Joint Meeting in Beijing, Nov. 21-23, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 73)
      - Ithaca Meeting, Dec. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 74)
      - Malcolm C. Bourne, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 75)
      - Trip Report, Mar.-Apr. 1984 (Box 28, Folder 76)
      - CUDP II, May 1984 (Box 28, Folder 77)
      - Royal Society, June 12-14, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 78)
      - Fall China Mission, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 79)
      - Honeywell Memo, Dec. 8, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 80)
      - F.W. McLafferty, 1984-1985 (Box 28, Folder 81)
      - Physics Disciplinary Report, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 82)
      - Fall Evaluation Trip to China, Aug. 30, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 83)
      - Executive Summaries - Beijing and Qinghua Universities, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 84)
      - Final China Visit, May 1986 (Box 28, Folder 85)
      - Joint Policy Meeting Minutes Nanjing, PRC, Nov. 15-17, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Siemens Software Seminars, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - CUDPII, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
      - CUDPII-Irvine, CA, May 1988 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Joint Policy Meeting-Irvine, CA, May 23-25, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - CUDPII, Fall 1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Evaluation Materials, Nov. 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Agenda, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - IAP Reports, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - CUDPII, June 1989 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - CUDPII, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - CUDPII, July 1989 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Cambridge Meeting, Oct. 18, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - CUDPII-Joint Policy Meeting, Spring 1990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - CUDPII (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
      - Final Project Evaluation-Univ. of Electronic Science and Technology, Sept. 1990 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Final Project Evaluation-Chengdu Univ. of Science and Technology, Southwest Jiatong Univ., Sept. 1990 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Final Evaluation-China Textile Univ., East China Inst. of Chemical Technology, Sept. 1990 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Beijing Hotel (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - DRC-Nates (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Typestyles (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Control Data China Inc. (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - American Embassy (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Mission from Chinese MOE (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Equipment Procurement (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - China Laboratory Centers to be Strengthened (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - China New Otani Hotel (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - Zhang Guangdon Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Xie Xide Correspondence, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 32-33)
      - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 35-36)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 36-A)
      - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Sub-subseries: Specialists and project staff
      - "Job Description" of Advisory Panel (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Proposed Candidates for Cochairmen of Chinese Advisory Panel (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Request to Establish Position: Executive Officer, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Appointment to Panel, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Appointment Papers (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Chinese Review Commission (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - World Bank - Clausen Bios (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Appointment of H. Beemer Staff Officer, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Bruce W. Jentleson, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Mark Kae (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Lennart Sandgren, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - D. Francis Finn (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Lars Ernster (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Professor Otto Schnepp (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Jean-Marie Pierre Lehn (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Robert Marshak (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Li Mingde's Address, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - DRC Appointment, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - DRC Business Cards (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Member List Chinese Review Commission (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Personnel Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Jodie Wisniewski (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Professor Xie Xi-de (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Betsy Toll, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Denver Research Institute, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - E.C. Slater, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - David Roy Watkins/Beijing, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - P.L. Richards/Nanjing, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - N. Wirth/Nanjing, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence - Consultants, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence - Consultants, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Specialists, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - B.T.K. Yakub/Nanjing, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - C.E. Munche, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Wietze Eizeuge (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - Thomas A. Detemple, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - Paul P.W. Cheng (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - Li Haiyan (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - Yu Desheng (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - Calvin Quate, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - B. Widrow - Qinghua, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - J.C. Anderson - Shandong, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - M.J. Miller - Shandong, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - R.J. Nelmes, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - H.F. Meiners/Xian Jiaotong, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - W.E. Cooke - Zhejiang, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - DeTemple/Zhongshan, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - A. Lohmann - Sichuan, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - S.L. Hsu/Tianjin, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - H. Matsumoto - Wuhan, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - Tomohiro Oguchi, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - Maponopo Sasa, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - C.T. Sah/Xiamen, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - P.M. Ribbe - Nanjing, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - H.F. Deutsch - Nanjing (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - R.Loudon - Lanzhou (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - A. Wagendristel - Jilian, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 59)
      - A. Vogelpohl - Huazhong, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 60)
      - Hsiung Hsu (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - P.Y. Yu - Fudan (Box 30, Folder 62)
      - Suango Takuo (Box 30, Folder 63)
      - Y.R. Shen (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - Pierpont/Fudan (Box 30, Folder 65)
      - E.M. Purcell - Fudan, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 66)